thebachelorguy.com 2013-05-19

# Static » Privacy Policy

TheBachelorGuy.com takes the privacy of our subscribers very seriously. (Believe me, I understand the meaning of the word “discreet”) This policy will describe how we handle the information you provide us when you visit the site, subscribe and/or answer questions.

Any personal information I ask for, such as your email address, is strictly to provide you with my daily emails and any other communications you may request. This information will only be used to provide you with these communications.

TheBachelorGuy.com may, for purposes of a specific promotion, survey, questionnaire, or other data gathering instance, ask for additional personal information, such as geographical location or your name. You may choose to provide this information, or not. Any personal information gathered will remain with TheBachelorGuy.com and will not be sold, leased, lent, shared, or leaked to any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission.

In order to make improvements and enhance your TheBachelorGuy.com experience I may periodically ask for non-personal information such as income, buying habits, occupation, hobbies, etc. This information may also be shared with potential advertisers and marketing partners. No personally identifying information about you will be shared.

My crack staff of web gurus needs certain information to keep the site running optimally. Between bouts of Unreal Tournament they gather information on usage of the site, such as what pages are most popular, how long visitors stay on the site, etc. We don’t collect personal information while doing this, just aggregated statistics and information.

As part of how TheBachelorGuy.com operates we do drop cookies, small text files, onto your hard drive. This is to allow us to recognize you as a subscriber, let’s you place items in your Bachelor Pad archive, etc. We do not retrieve any information from a computer unrelated to our site or services. Our third party advertisers may place a cookie as part of serving ads on our site.

As part of TheBachelorGuy.com editorials we may provide links to third party sites. TheBachelorGuy.com is not responsible for content on those sites, and does not endorse them. You will have to read the policies of each site and determine whether or not to continue using those sites and/or providing them with information.

\-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

CPX Interactive is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users.

Accordingly, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, and will continue to review and improve our privacy policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of consumer information. This Privacy Statement presents our privacy policy, including CPX Interactive's privacy practices for our web site. Below is information regarding CPX Interactive's commitment to protecting the privacy of Internet users.  
Consumer Information

CPX Interactive uses one or more third party ad serving technology to serve ads at this site and at our clients' sites. In the course of delivering an ad to you, the third party ad serving party may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser and use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this non-personally-identifiable information used to serve ads to you, please click here.  
Cookies and Opt Out

Like most Internet sites, CPX Interactive and its third party ad serving party uses "cookies" to enhance the Internet user's experience on the Web. Neither CPX Interactive nor such third party ad serving party uses these cookies to personally identify you in any way, and these cookies in no way damage your system or files.  
What are cookies and how do they enhance your Web experience?

A cookie is a unique number that is assigned to you the first time you are served an ad. This number is stored in a file on your computer. For instance, cookies help ensure that you don't repeatedly see the same ad. Cookies can also help advertisers measure how you utilize an advertiser's site and the effectiveness of an ad. This information can then be used by advertisers to better cater to your needs. In other words, cookies help us deliver to you the types of ads in which you are more interested.

Although we believe that cookies help enhance your experience on the Web (by not repeatedly serving the same ads to you and delivering more relevant messages to you), neither CPX Interactive nor its third party ad serving party needs cookies to deliver ads to you.  
Opt Out

If you do not want the benefits of cookies, there is a simple procedure that allows you to deny or accept this feature. In order to "opt out" of the benefits of cookies, you may either manually delete your cookies by following the instructions contained in the Help section of your browser, or you may click here.  
Industry Efforts to Protect Consumer Privacy

CPX Interactive is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Accordingly, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, including those established by the Direct Marketing Association. To review information regarding privacy practices on our CPX Interactive Web site, please click here. If you should have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact our Customer Services at contact@cpxinteractive.com. We recommend that you periodically review this Privacy Statement, as CPX Interactive may update it from time to time.  
Third Party Advertising

We use CPX Interactive INC and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here  
Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Any changes to TheBachelorGuy.com privacy policy will be posted here. If you have any questions just pop me **[here.](http://www.thebachelorguy.com/contact/)**
